[Music]
[音乐]
Inkscape recently introduced version 1.0
Inkscape最近推出了1.0版
as a new release and this was not your
作为新版本，而这不是您的
typical update this new release comes
这个新版本的典型更新是
packed with lots of new features and
充斥着许多新功能和
functionality that might make your life
可能会让你的生活
a little easier as an Inkscape user I'll
作为一名Inkscape用户，我将
have a link in the description to the
在描述中有指向
wiki page with a complete list of all
包含完整列表的Wiki页面
the new features and updates added if
如果添加了新功能和更新，
you want to check that out but in this
你想看看这个，但在这个
video I'd just like to go over a few of
我只想回顾一下几个视频
those features that I'm really excited
那些让我非常兴奋的功能
about in particular and if you are
特别是如果你是
enrolled in my Inkscape masterclass I
报名参加我的Inkscape大师班
have updated the course contents
已更新课程内容
according to the new release and if
根据新版本，如果
you're not enrolled maybe consider
你没有注册，也许可以考虑
checking it out if you want to learn
如果你想学习，就去看看吧
more about Inkscape I'll have a link in
有关Inkscape的更多信息，我将在
the description for more information
有关更多信息的说明
about that as well
关于那件事也是
to get us started Inkscape has
为了让我们开始，Inkscape已经
officially added support for theme
官方添加了对主题的支持
customization gone are the days where we
定制的日子一去不复返了
had to tinker with system files and
不得不修补系统文件和
perform other types of voodoo magic just
表演其他类型的巫毒魔法
to get a more visually appealing dark
为了得到视觉上更吸引人的黑暗
theme with a more modern icon pack it's
主题与更现代的图标包它是
now built right in you can just navigate
现在内置了，您只需导航
to edit preferences and click on theme
编辑首选项并单击主题
under the interface tab and from there
在接口选项卡下，然后从那里
you can choose from a variety of themes
您可以从各种主题中进行选择
and yes that does include a dark theme
是的，这确实包括了一个黑暗的主题
not only that but you can also switch to
不仅如此，您还可以切换到
a more modern icon pack with the
更现代的图标包，配有
monochromatic style that looks more like
单色风格，看起来更像
it belongs in the year 2020 you can even
它属于2020年，你甚至可以
go as far as changing the color of those
甚至改变了那些的颜色
icons if you so desire
图标，如果你愿意的话
one new feature that I'm really excited
一项让我非常兴奋的新功能
about an Inkscape version 1.0 has to do
关于Inkscape 1.0版必须做的事情
with the text tool if you generate some
如果您生成了一些
text on your canvas you'll notice that
你会注意到画布上的文字
there's now a little note on the bottom
现在底部有一张小纸条
right side of your text item clicking
在文本项的右侧单击
and dragging that node will allow you to
拖动该节点将允许您
determine where a line of text should
确定文本行的位置
end this will be really useful when
在以下情况下结束此操作将非常有用
designing things like brochures where
设计宣传册之类的东西
you have to confine your text to a
您必须将文本限制在
specific vertical column you won't have
您将不会有特定的垂直栏
to worry about making the bounding box
担心制作包围盒的问题
of that text fit that column any longer
不再适合那一栏了
you can simply adjust that node to make
您只需调整该节点即可使
your lines of text end exactly where you
您的文本行在您的
want
想要
those of you who use illustrator may
使用Illustrator的用户可以
already be familiar with the concept of
已经熟悉……的概念
outline mode which allows you to view
大纲模式，允许您查看
your design as somewhat of a skeleton
你的设计有点像骨架
where you can see all of the individual
在那里你可以看到所有的个体
paths and boundaries that make up a
路径和边界组成了
design without fill colors and other
没有填充颜色和其他颜色的设计
design elements getting in the way this
设计元素阻碍了这一点
is useful because sometimes you need to
是很有用的，因为有时您需要
select or work with a particular object
选择或使用特定对象
but you can't select it because you
但您不能选择它，因为您
don't know where it is because it's
不知道它在哪里，因为它是
positioned beneath other objects with
定位在其他对象的下方，使用
fill data this is one of the reasons why
填充数据这是原因之一
I tend to make objects with partial
我倾向于用局部来制作物品
transparency when I'm designing
我在设计时的透明度
something you just need to be able to
一些你只需要能够做到的事情
know where things are sometimes and
有时知道东西在哪里，
Inkscape has now made that easier with
Inkscape现在让这一点变得更容易了
their own version of outline mode and
他们自己版本的大纲模式和
I'll even go as far as saying that
我甚至可以这么说
they've outdone illustrator with this
他们在这方面胜过了插图画家
update because it offers a lot more
更新，因为它提供了更多
versatility the first way you can view
多功能性是您可以查看的第一种方式
your work in outline mode is by
您在大纲模式下的工作由
navigating to the View menu and clicking
导航到查看菜单，然后单击
on x-ray mode this will allow you to use
在x射线模式下，这将允许您使用
your cursor as somewhat of a viewfinder
您的光标有点像取景器
where you can hover it over specific
在那里您可以将其悬停在特定的
areas of your design to see all of the
您的设计区域，以查看所有
individual outlines the second way you
个人概述您的第二种方式
can view your design is outlines is by
可以查看您的设计的轮廓是由
navigating to the View menu and
导航到视图菜单，然后
selecting split view mode this will
选择拆分视图模式，这将
generate a guide through the center of
生成通过中心的辅助线
your screen
您的屏幕
that will show how your design normally
这将显示您的设计如何正常
looks on one side and how it looks an
看起来是一边的，看起来是什么样子
outline mode on the other side you can
轮廓模式在另一面，您可以
move the guide around by clicking and
通过单击和移动辅助线
dragging it and you can also change the
拖动它，您还可以更改
orientation and position of your guide
导游的方向和位置
by clicking on the individual arrows
通过单击各个箭头
if you open up your align and distribute
如果您打开您的对齐和分发
menu you'll notice a new icon in the top
你会注意到顶部有一个新的图标
left portion of the menu labeled enable
菜单左侧标有Enable的部分
on canvas alignment handles if you hover
如果将鼠标悬停在画布对齐句柄上
your cursor over it enabling that icon
将光标放在其上即可启用该图标
will allow you to align objects directly
将允许您直接对齐对象
on the canvas without having to use the
在画布上，无需使用
alignment menu interface the way that it
对齐菜单的界面方式是它
works is that you select the objects
它的工作原理是选择对象
you'd like to align click on them once
您想要对齐它们，只需点击一次
to display the rotation handles then
要显示旋转手柄，则
click on them a second time to display
再次单击它们即可显示
the new alignment handles then from
然后，新的对齐句柄从
there you can simply click on those
在那里，您只需单击这些
handles to align your objects the same
控制柄以相同的方式对齐对象
way you normally would in the align and
以您通常会在Align和
distribute menu this is a unique feature
分发菜单这是一项独特的功能
that I have not seen anywhere else and
我在其他任何地方都没见过
it's one of those things that you didn't
这是你没有做过的事情之一
know you needed until you tried it
我知道你需要，直到你试过
another new feature that I know I'll be
另一个我知道我会成为的新功能
using a lot is the new offset live path
使用Lot是新的Offset Live路径
effect this functions very similarly to
效果这一功能非常类似于
the standard dynamic offset path
标准动态偏移路径
operation only with one very big
只有一个非常大的手术
improvement and that is that it now
改进，那就是现在
allows you to maintain sharp corners
使您可以保持锐角
to see what I mean if you were to
去了解我的意思，如果你
perform a dynamic offset on an object
对对象执行动态偏移
with sharp corners like a star you'll
像星星一样的尖角，你会发现
notice that the corners become rounded
请注意，这些角变圆了
as you offset the object this is fine
当您对对象进行偏移时，这很好
for objects with rounded corners but
用于圆角对象，但
it's useless in scenarios where you need
在您需要的情况下，它毫无用处
to maintain the sharp corners of an
若要保持一个
object my workaround for dealing with
反对我处理以下问题的解决方法
this in the past was to offset the
这在过去是为了抵消
object by adding a stroke with sharp
通过添加带有锐化的笔触来创建
corners then convert the stroke to a
然后，角点将笔划转换为
path to work with it further now those
现在进一步使用它的路径是
days are over thanks to the new offset
由于有了新的补偿，日子已经过去了
live path effect which allows you to
实时路径效果，允许您
maintain sharp corners on an object as
将对象的锐角保持为
you offset it to access the new feature
您需要对其进行偏移才能访问新功能
select the object you'd like to offset
选择要偏移的对象
then navigates a path and path effects
然后导航路径和路径效果
to bring up the path effects window then
要调出路径效果窗口，然后
click on the little plus sign to add a
单击小加号以添加
new path effects and from the path
新路径效果和来自路径
effects menu search for offset and apply
效果菜单搜索偏移并应用
that then you can grab the edit pads by
这样你就可以通过以下方式抓取编辑板
nodes tool and use the little node to
节点工具，并使用小节点来
offset your object while maintaining
在保持对象的同时偏移对象
sharp corners
尖角
excape version 1.0 comes with lots of
Excape1.0版附带了许多
welcomed improvements like support for
受欢迎的改进，如支持
high-resolution displays if you're using
如果您使用的是
a 4k monitor you'll actually be able to
一台4K显示器，你实际上可以
see the user interface now there's also
请看用户界面，现在还有
some other subtle changes like in the
其他一些微妙的变化，如
way that stroke to path works when you
笔划到路径的工作方式当您
convert a stroke to a path it now
立即将笔划转换为路径
retains the fill segment of that stroke
保留该笔触的填充线段
as a separate object like I mentioned
作为一个单独的对象，就像我提到的
earlier there's lots of new updates and
早些时候有很多新的更新
details to comb through so be sure to
要梳理的细节，所以一定要
check out that wiki page for a complete
请查看该维基页面以获取完整的
overview let me know what you think of
概述让我知道你的想法
the new version of Inkscape in the
新版本的Inkscape在
comments below and as always thanks for
下面的评论，并一如既往地感谢
watching
观看
[Music]
[音乐]